三年前...
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： rosemaryai  tony  宝宝宝  veronique
翻译： Isaac   字幕总监：lonelyatta  梁良
■
时间轴： 灰灰小朋友 校对：  许愿
伙计  他们会发现的
Dude, they'll find out.
口风紧点就行
Not if we stick to the story.
我不知道  Jack  这么做可能有危险
I don't know, jack. it could be a risk.
这是唯一的办法  我们必须得这么做
It's the only way. We have to do this.
他们还没决定是吗
they're still at it, huh?
我们没有时间了
Look, we're running out of time.
现在就得做决定
We gotta make a decision now.
大家都同意这样做吗
So are we all okay with this?
这个决定会影响我们的余生
This is a decision that will affect the rest of our lives.
我不会草率地决定
I'm not taking it lightly.
Kate
Kate?
我同意
Yeah.
Sun
Sun?
-Frank  -什么事
- Frank? - what?
很抱歉把你卷进来
Sorry you got dragged into this,
但是我们得知道你和我们是一致的
But we need to know that you're with us.
不管你们怎么决定  我都同意
Whatever you guys decide, I'll just roll with.
Hurley  你怎么想
Hurley, what about you?
我们不该撒谎  伙计
I don't think we should lie, dude.
Hurley  我们得保护留下的那些人
We need to protect the people that we left behind, hurley.
撒谎怎么能保护他们
How does lying protect them?
可以保护他们不受Charles Widmore的伤害
It protects them from charles widmore.
那家伙雇了一批人要杀了我们
The guy hired a boatload of people to kill all of us.
他伪造了飞机失事
He faked a plane crash.
你认为告诉他实话以后
I mean, you think telling him the truth,
他还能放过他们
He's just gonna-- he's gonna leave them alone?
他是你老爸  是吗
Look, he's your dad, right?
你不能让他罢手吗
Can't you, like... call him off?
没有什么能阻止我父亲
There's no calling my father off.
但是他永远都不会找到他们
But he'll never find them.
那小岛消失了
I mean, the island disappeared.
我们都看到了
We all saw it. it's gone.
"噗"的一下
Bloop!
你认为有人会相信...
You think anyone's gonna believe that...
这无稽之谈吗
Believe any of it?
他们会认为你疯了
They're gonna think you're crazy.
如果有人给我作证就不会
Not if someone backs me up.
Sayid  来吧
Sayid, come on.
如果我说实话  他们会认为我是个白痴
They'll think I'm nuts if I tell the truth.
但是如果我们都说实话会怎样呢
But what if we all do?
如果我们能为彼此作证
And if we can stick together,
就会让他们相信我们
we can make 'em believe us.
我不想下半辈子活在谎言里
I don't want to spend the rest of my life lying.
-你想吗  -不想
- do you? - no.
但是
But...
我们没有更好的选择
I don't believe we have a better choice.
我很抱歉  Hurley  但是我们必须得撒谎
I'm sorry, hurley, but we have to lie.
你知道吗  伙计
You know what, dude?
我会记住你的所作所为
I'm gonna remember this.
有一天  你会需要我帮忙
And someday, you're gonna need my help,
我现在就告诉你
And I'm telling you right now...
我不会帮你
You're not gettin' it.
醒醒  Sayid
Wake up, sayid!
Sayid
Sayid!
Sayid  醒醒
Sayid, wake up!
Sayid
Sayid!
不不不  我该怎么做
No, no, no, no, no! what do I do?!
我应该怎么做
What am I supposed to do?!
好了  好了  好了
Okay, okay, okay.
保持冷静
Just stay calm.
你到底想什么呢
What the hell were you thinking?
-Ana Lucia  -你像个疯子一样开车
- Ana lucia? - you were driving like a maniac.
还有  你为什么靠边停车
And why'd you pull over?
我只是  我  我想
I just... i-i thought--
如果我是真的你该怎么办
You didn't think. what if I were real?
如果真的有警察拦住你怎么办
What if a real cop stopped you?
他们有你浑身染血
They already have pictures of you covered in blood
-手里还拿着枪  -实际上  那些是番茄酱
- With a gun in your hand. - actually, it's ketchup.
我们去了快餐店...然后...
We went to a-a drive-thru, and, uh....
你得振作起来
Well, you need to pull it together.
-你有许多事情要做  -是吗
- You've got a lot of work to do. - I do?
从最基本的开始  首先  你需要新衣服
Let's start with the basics. first off, you need new clothes.
然后你得去个安全的地方
Then you need to go to a safe place.
把Sayid带到某个你信任的人那里去
And take sayid to somebody you trust.
-你都听懂了吗  -是的
- You getting all this? - yeah.
那就开始干吧
Then get to it.
还要远离警察
And stay away from the cops.
别被抓到
Do not get arrested.
谢谢  Ana Lucia
Thanks, ana lucia.
对了  Libby向你问好
Oh, yeah. libby says hi.
听她的
You heard her.
你真的认为那东西有用
You really think that thing's gonna work?
Rose  我告诉你上百次了
Rose, I told you a hundred times.
当然会有用  是的  我努力这么做
Of course it's gonna work. yes. I worked hard on it.
这比把两根棍子放在一起磨擦有效
It's better than rubbing two sticks together.
就该这么做,
That's what you supposed to do
是吗  我认为这个更有效  好吗
Yeah? well, I think this is gonna work better, all right?
我认为你在里面木头放太多了
Well, I think you got too much wood here in the inside.
这会把叶子盖住
That's gonna smother the leaves.
Rose  如果没有足够的木头,叶子不会着起来的
Rose, if you don't have enough wood, the leaves just burn out.
生火  谁在乎生火啊
Fire? who cares about fire?
天空随时随刻都会发光
Any minute the sky could light up,
谁他妈的知道这次会发生什么
And who the hell knows what could happen this time?
Neil  我们正全力做我们能控制的事情
Neil, we are trying to focus on what we can control.
你要么帮忙要么闭嘴
You are either gonna help or be quiet!
-这是谁的衬衫  -是我的
- Whose shirt is this? - it's mine.
能给我吗
Can I have it?
这有什么要紧  我们日落的时候就会死去
what does it matter? we're all gonna be dead by sundown.
我认为这表示你同意  哈蚂脸
I'll take that as a "yes," frogurt.
-我叫Neil  -是啊  是啊
- It's neil. - yeah, yeah.
这个仍然完好吗
Still in one piece?
据我所知是的
As far as I can tell.
我认为船和其他成员一起消失了
I figured it would've disappeared With the rest of our stuff.
我认为航行中我们所携带的东西
I guess whatever we had with us when we moved
都一起消失了
Is along for the ride.
怎么啦
What?
看谁回来了
Look who's back.
欢迎回来  魔法教授
Welcome back, dr. wizard.
-我说他是魔法先生  -闭嘴
I think it's mr. wizard. shut up.
你离开了2个小时  你到底在干什么
You've been gone for two hours. what the hell were you doing?
是啊  完全正确  我很抱歉
Yeah, you're absolutely right. I'm sorry.
我的包落在丛林里了  我回来了
I...  left my pack in the jungle and I was coming back
并且  我  我  只是  过了一段时间
And i-i-i just--it was a while before I realized
我才意识到我  我迷路了
That I was just... uh, I was really lost.
你算出来天空何时再次发光了吗
Well, you figure out when the sky's gonna light up again?
我不知道  好吧  你至少有个计划吧
I don't know. well, you at least got a plan?
我认为我们应该拿着罗盘
I think we should take the zodiac,
-前往某条航运航线  -不行  不行
- Head to a shipping lane. - no. no, no, no.
任何情况下我们都不能出航
We can't just sail out on any course.
如果要离开  我得重新测算方位
For us to leave, I need to calculate a new bearing,
而且  为了定位
And, uh, to do that...
我需要确定我们的位置...
I need to determine where we are now...
在时间里
Time.
那剩下的人应该做什么呢
And what are the rest of us supposed to do?
我去给我们找点吃的
I'm gonna go find us something to eat.
你计划怎么做呢
And how are you planning on doing that?
别担心
Don't worry about it.
我们找水去
I guess we'll get the water.
伙计  醒醒啊
Dude, wake up!
醒醒  我一个人做不了这些
Come on. I can't do this on my own!
我保证我会补偿你的
I promise I'll pay you back.
在这等着
Wait right here.
西施犬
Shih tzus?
我喜欢这只西施犬
I like shih tzus.
看起来你把他们爱到心窝里去了
It looks like you "heart" them.
不愉快的夜晚
Rough night?
嗯
Yeah.
你朋友很颓废
Your friend's pretty wasted.
嗯
Yeah.
你很眼熟啊
I know you from somewhere, don't i?
-不  -我认为是的
No. I think I do.
-你看起来很眼熟  -只是大众脸罢了
Yeah, you definitely look familiar. I just have one of those faces.
你在撒谎
You're lying.
我不认为我在撒谎
I don't believe in lying.
我记得
I remember!
你是那个中了大奖的人
You're the guy who won the lottery...
你坐的飞机坠毁了
And you crashed in that plane.
-不  我绝对是长得和他像  -你就是他  在这买张彩票
No. I must look like him. you're him. hey! buy a ticket here.
如果你中了 我拿回扣 你运气真好哦
If you win, we get a commission. you're good luck.
对不起  你认错人了  不用找了
Sorry. wrong dude. keep the change.
好吧
Okay.
好的 我们离开这里
Okay, we're outta here.
妈妈  我想回家
Mommy, I wanna go home.
看你的书吧 宝宝
Look at your book, baby.
喂
Hello?
我不敢相信是你
I-i can't believe it's you.
不
No. hi.
你好吗
How are you?
等等  你在洛杉矶
Wait, you're in l.a.?
我当然能来  什么...
Of course I can meet, yeah. what...
我很清楚那是哪儿 我会在半小时内到
I know exactly where that is. I'll be there in half an hour.
妈妈  我们去哪儿
Mommy, where are we going?
去见一个朋友
To see a friend.
你在找你的药片吗? Jack
You looking for your pills, jack?
我把他们扔在马桶里冲走了
I flushed them down the toilet.
谢谢
Thank you.
我只是想自己做
I was just gonna do that myself.
是的 我猜你也是
Yeah, I figured you were.
要去哪儿
Going somewhere?
退房
I'm checking out.
我们去哪里
Where are we going?
你回家 然后自己找到一个手提箱
You're going home. and find yourself a suitcase.
如果有什么你要的东西在里面
If there's anything in this life you want,
装进去
ck it in there...
因为你绝不会回来了
Because you're never coming back.
好的
Good.
很好
我六小时后来接你
I'll pick you up in six hours.
那你要去哪儿
And where will you be going?
John的灵柩在外面一个小货车里
John's casket is outside in a carpet van.
我要把他转移到安全的地方去
I need to move it somewhere safe.
安全
Safe?
他死了 对吗
He's dead, isn't he?
六小时后见  Jack
I'll see you in six hours, jack.
"expose"前提回顾
> previously on "expos?...
看起来"蝎子"已经在接管
It looks like the scorpion is taking over
所有"眼镜蛇"的生意了
All the cobra's business.
你要我和"海啸"工作
You want me to work with tsunami,
-凡奈斯恐龙女吗  -是的
- The dragon lady of van nuys? - Yeah.
我就在这儿抓那蝎子
I'm here to capture the scorpion,
如果你有什么问题  可以去第三舞台
So if you've got a problem with that, you can go work stage 3.
老爸
Hey, dad.
还好吗
How's it going?
我刚睡醒  为什么这么说  你又被通缉了
No. I just got up. why, are you wanted again?
可以这么说
Uh, yeah. kinda.
-妈在吗  -不  她出去购物了  把他放这儿
Is mom here? no, she's out shopping.hey, set him over
-上帝  他晕过去了  -他还在...呼吸吗
Oh, man, he's out. is he... breathing?
勉强  发生什么事了
Barely. what happened?
-他被飞镖射中了  -飞镖  什么  你们在动物园还是哪里
He got shot by a dart. a dart? what, were you in the zoo or something?
不  我们在安全屋里  -安全屋
No, we were at the safe house. the safe house?
Sayid把我带到这为了保护我
Sayid took me there to protect me.
然后那两个人用飞镖射中了他
Then these two guys jumped down, they shot him with darts,
-他现在就昏迷了  -Hugo  这讲不通
And now he's--he's in a coma or something. hugo, this doesn't make sense.
你出了精神病院都做了什么
And what are you doing out of the mental institution?
Sayid把我带出来  我们很危险
Sayid pulled me out. I'm in danger. we both are.
谁想害你们
Danger from who?
我不是很确定
I'm not sure exactly.
喂
Hello?
是Reyes家吗
Mr. and mrs. reyes?
洛杉矶警察  请你们打开门
L.a.p.d. can you open the gate, please
你有什么麻烦
Just what kind of trouble are you in?
爸  拜托  不要告诉他们我在这儿
Dad, please! just don't tell 'em I'm here!
好的  不过你要告诉我真相
All right, but then you're gonna tell me the truth.
如果有什么情况请给我们回电
Well, give us a call if you hear anything.
你杀了3个人
You killed three people?
不是我 sayid杀的
No. sayid did.
那还好点 快,我们把他弄到沙发上
Oh,well, that's better. Come on. let's get him to the couch.
-他救了我  -我觉得我们现在要请个律师
He saved me. I think we should call a lawyer right now.
不  我们不能出去  他们正在找我们
No, no, no. we can't go public. they're after us.
谁  谁在找你们
Who? who is after you?
我不知道  Sayid知道  他能解释
I don't know. sayid knows. he can explain.
Sayid没有说什么
Sayid ain't explaining nothing.
我们要把他送医院去
We need to get him to a hospital.
你没有听见我说的吗  有人想杀我们
Did you not hear me? people are trying to kill us.
我们去了医院  他们就会找到我们
We go to a hospital, they'll find us!
就像"教父"里  你最不该去的地方
Like--like "the godfather." it's the last place you go.
他们会用枕头闷死你还伪装成是一场意外
Everyone knows it.they smother you with pillows And make it look like an accident.
Sayid  快醒醒
Sayid, please wake up!
没用的  我们得找个医生
That's not gonna work. We need a doctor.
我知道该怎么做了
I think I know what to do.
妈妈  能让我来按钮吗
Mommy, mommy, can I push the button?
当然可以  宝贝
Sure you can, sweetie.
我们要直达顶楼  知道吗
But we're all the way to the top, okay?
所以你要按3-1  看到了吗
So I want you to press number 3-1. You see it?
看到了吗  好  按吧  3-1
You see it? Okay. You get it. 3-1.
没错  就是那个
Yeah! That's the one!
按到了  按到了
You pressed it! You pressed it!
你好
Hi.
你好  Kate
Hello, Kate.
祝你今天愉快
Have a nice day.
我马上来
I'll be right with you.
你好  Ben
Hello, Ben.
如果你要牛排  我们卖完了
If it's the porterhouse you're looking for, we're out.
不  今天不了
No, no porterhouse.
但是  Jill  我的货车里
I do, however, have something
的确有些重要东西
Very important in my van, Jill,
我想让你帮忙照看一下
And I need you to watch it for me.
-是我想象中的东西吗  -是的
- Is it what I think it is? - It is.
放心交给我吧
He'll be safe with me.
-Gabriel和Jeffrey登记过了吗  -是
- Have Gabriel and Jeffrey checked in yet? - Yeah.
一切都按照计划进行
Everything's moving right on schedule.
-跟Shephard谈得怎么样了  -他入伙了
- How's it going with Shephard? - He's with us.
是吗  你怎么做的  给他吃了迷魂药吗
Really? What'd you do, bribe him with some pills?
我放了他一马
Cut the man some slack.
他的日子不好过  我们都是
He's been through a lot. We all have.
没错  当然
Right. Of course.
对不起
Sorry.
所以保证他的安全  Jill
So keep him safe, Jill.
如果你不这么做
Because if you don't...
我们所计划的一切
Everything we're about to do...
都会前功尽弃
Won't matter at all.
成功了  成功了
Oh, you got it! You got it! You got it!
成功了  成功了  好了  终于成功了
You got it. You got it. All right! Finally we got...
怎么会那样
Why did you do that?
你应该赶快扇火的  Rose
Because you're supposed to fan the flame, Rose.
我还以为你知道该怎么生火呢
I thought you said you knew how to start a fire.
我还以为你不在乎呢
And I thought you said you didn't care.
我只在乎如何生存
I care about surviving.
我觉得你可以闭上嘴了  Neil
I think you need to take a time-out, Neil.
-你会成功的  Bernard  -好  好的
- You'll get it, Bernard. You will. - Yeah. All right.
再试试看
Just--just try again.
请稍等
Give me one second.
给你看点东西
I got you something.
我在树林里发现的
I found these in the jungle.
-太好了  谢谢  -只有两个
- Look at that. Thank you. -There was only two,
但我觉得够我们填填肚子了
But I thought we could both do with a bite to eat.
谢谢  太谢谢你了
Thank you very much, very much.
你还好吧
You all right?
我就是没办法摆脱这该死的头痛
I just can't seem to shake this bloody headache.
好了  我相信会好的
Well... I'm sure it'll pass.
不  不只是那个
No, it's not just that.
最奇怪的是  前一秒钟  我还在...
It's the weirdest thing. Earlier, I was...
我还在想我妈妈
I was thinking about my mom,
突然之前  我竟然记不起她的闺名了
And all of sudden, I-I couldn't remember her maiden name.
这难道不奇怪吗
I mean, isn't that odd?
听着  所有人都承受着很大的压力
Listen, all of us have been under a lot of stress. Okay?
Daniel
Daniel...
你知道在我身上发生了什么吗
Do you know what's happening to me?
开饭了
Dinner!
太棒了  你从哪弄来的
That's great! Wow! Where'd you get that?
我发现了它
I found it.
你说"发现"是什么意思
What do you mean you "found" it?
它死在树林里  我发现了它
It died in the jungle. I found it.
别担心  没事的  刚死了三个小时
Don't worry. It's fine. It's only been dead three hours.
什么
What?
谁有刀
Who's got a knife?
刀  你要刀吗
A knife? You need a knife?
就在烤箱旁边
Oh, it's over by the Cuisinart next to the stove.
你在说什么
What's your problem?
我是说  我们根本就没有刀
My problem is, we don't have a knife.
我们什么都没有
W-we don't have anything.
即使我们有了也无济于事
And it wouldn't even matter if we did,
因为那个牙医Bernie连火都没生起来
'Cause Bernie the dentist can't even start a fire.
放松点  哈蚂脸
Hey, ease up there, Frogurt.
我叫Neil  你个傻瓜
It's Neil, you inbred.
我可放松不了
And I'm not gonna ease up,
因为我又累又饿  糟透了
'Cause I'm tired and I'm hungry and I'm screwed!
-我们都糟透了  -冷静点  Neil
- We're all screwed! - Calm down, Neil.
我们会挺过去的
We're gonna get through this.
我们怎么可能挺过去
How are any of us gonna get through this?!
你没听到我说的吗  我们连火都生不起来
Didn't you hear what I just said?! We can't even get fire!
快跑
Run!
快点  分开  大家都到小溪那里去
Come on! Split up! Everybody, get to the creek!
Dan
Ow! Dan!
快跑
Keep moving!
快走  他死了
Come on. He's dead.
快点  你也想送死吗  快点
Come on! You wanna be dead, too?! Come on!
你做不了什么  我们得赶快跑
There's nothing you coulda done. We gotta go now!
他们在监视我们吗
Dude, they're on a stakeout?
你刚从精神病院中逃出来
You just escaped from a mental institution.
还死了人
There's dead bodies everywhere!
他们当然要监视我们
Of course they're on a stakeout!
他们认为你疯到要回家来
They think you're crazy enough to come back home.
你是不是...
S-so are you...
疯了
Crazy?
你觉得我是吗
Do you think I am?
否则你就是在骗我
Well, either that or you're lying to me.
我没疯
I'm not crazy,
而且我欺骗你是有原因的
And I have a really good reason why I'm lying to you.
什么原因
Well, what is it?
我沙发上怎么会有个巴基斯坦死人
Why is there a dead pakistani on my couch?!
他没死  妈妈
He's not dead, ma.
但他没气了
Well, he's not breathing.
没气了吗
He's not?!
没关系  Carmen  我们有个计划
It's okay, Carmen. We have a plan.
计划  你们在说什么
A plan? What are you talking about?
他还有气...算有吧  爸  我们要走了
He is breathing... kind of. Dad, we gotta go now.
Hugo  发生了什么
Hugo, what's happening?
妈  拜托
Mom, please!
别跟我说"妈  拜托"  新闻里怎么都是你
No "mom, please" me! Why are you all over the news?
你知道他们怎么说你吗
Do you know what they are telling about you?
我知道  妈
Yeah, mom. I know.
一切都会真相大白的  我保证
Look, everything's gonna make sense. I promise.
但愿如此
It better!
长官
Officers.
你在洛杉矶待了多久
So how long are you in l.a.?
几天而已
Just a few days.
我来谈点公事
I have some business to attend to.
但是我一直很想见你
But I wanted to see you.
这呢
Here it is.
她叫Ji Yeon  这是她的照片
Her name's ji yeon. here's a baby picture.
她真漂亮
Oh! she's beautiful.
谢谢  她在首尔的外婆家
Thank you. she's with her grandmother in seoul.
希望有朝一日你们能够见面
I hope someday you get to meet her.
她和Aaron在一起玩一定很可爱
It would be nice to see her and aaron play together.
是啊
Yeah.
Kate  你还好吧
Kate? are you all right?
我很好
Yeah. I'm fine.
真的么
Are you?
有人知道我们在撒谎
Somebody knows we're lying.
什么
What?
几个律师去找过我
Some lawyers came to see me.
谁
Who?
两个男人  他们来过我家
Two men. they came to my house
要求我们验血
And they asked for a blood sample.
好像要起诉我们
Some kind of lawsuit.
他们想要检测
They wanted to test to see if...
Aaron是不是我的孩子
To see if aaron's my son.
哪里派来的律师
Who did these lawyers represent?
不知道  他们不告诉我他们的委托人是谁
I don't know. they wouldn't tell me who their client is.
那么说他们并不想将这个谎言公开
Then they're not interested in exposing the lie.
你怎么知道的
How do you know?
因为他们想的话  早就下手了
Because if they were, they would just do it.
他们不会私下找你
They wouldn't come to you in private.
他们并不关心我们是不是撒了谎  他们想要的是Aaron
They don't care that we're lying. they just want aaron.
但是  谁会想要这么做
But who... who would do that? we--
我不知道  但是你要解决他们
I don't know, but you need to take care of them.
什么叫解决他们
What do you mean, take care of them?
为了保护Aaron
Wouldn't you do anything you had to
你会在所不惜吧
In order to keep aaron?
你以为我是什么人
What kind of a person do you think I am?
Jin  jin
Jin! jin!
那种在危机关头会痛下决断的人
The kind of person who makes hard decisions when she has to.
你带着孩子上飞机  我去找Jin
You get the baby on the chopper. I'll get jin.
就像你在货船上做的那样
Like you did on the freighter.
你让我上飞机
You told me to get on the helicopter,
-你说你会找到Jin  -我们得赶快离开这里
- And you said you'd get jin. - We gotta get outta here!
Sun  我希望你不要误会
Sun, I hope you don't think...
你做了不得不做的事
But you did what you had to do.
如果你没有这么做
And if you hadn't...
我们可能全都死了  而不光是我的丈夫
We probably all would've died instead of just my husband.
对不起
I'm sorry.
真的对不起
I'm so sorry. i...
我没有怪你
I don't blame you.
说起来
So...
Jack现在怎么样
How's jack?
Hugo说我可以信任你
Hugo said I could trust you.
我不这么肯定  但是他发了誓  那么
I wasn't so sure. but he swore I could, so...
我可以信任你吗
Can i?
当然可以
Yes. of course.
好吧
All right.
他出什么事了
What happened to him?
Hugo说他给飞镖砸了
Hugo said he got hit with some dart.
肯定是嗑了药什么的
Must've been some drugs or something.
-Hurley现在在哪  -在家里  快崩溃了
- And where is hurley right now? - At our house, freaking out.
我去取我的车  帮我把他抬过来
Let me get my car. help me move h over.
送他上医院
I'm gonna have to get him to the hospital.
不行  Hugo说不管谁送他去医院
No. no, h-hugo said that whoever did this--
都会引火上身  为了你好  先生
They'll come back after him. all due respect, mr.
Reyes  是你带他找的我
Reyes, but you brought him to me,
-所以我会全部为Sayid着想  -那好吧
-So I'm gonna do what I think is best for sayid. -all right, fine.
带他去医院
Take him to the hospital.
Shephard大夫  你看我什么都听你的
But with all due respect to you, dr. shephard,
-等办完事  你要帮我个忙  -什么忙
-When this is over, you're gonna do something for me. -what?
离Hugo远点  不管你是怎么取信于Hugo的
Stay away from hugo. whatever it is you talked him into,
我有预感
Something tells me
你不会全心为他着想的
You don't have his best interests at heart.
所以你离我儿子远点
So stay away from my son.
你好
Hello?
Ben
Ben...
你肯定猜不出谁不请自来了
You'll never guess who just showed up my door
谁
Who?
Sayid
Sayid.
谁是Sayid
Who is sayid?
我以为他是你朋友
I thought he was your friend.
他是我朋友
He is my friend...
但他同时具有双重人生
But he's also got this double life
他那套忍者行动和间谍什么的
Where he does crazy ninja moves and spy stuff.
但是他是好人
But he's a good guy.
好人不会杀死三个人
A good guy doesn't kill three men.
好人不会杀任何人
A good guy doesn't kill any men.
-妈妈  -别叫我妈妈
-Mom  -Don't "mom" me.
Hugo  你麻烦大了
You are in terrible trouble, hugo.
新闻说是你杀的人
The news thinks you did this.
新闻这么说  人就会这么传
And if the news does, everyone does.
为什么会这样
Why is this happening?
怎么会有人想要伤害你
How can anybody want to hurt you?
我不知道
I don't know.
实话告诉妈妈
Tell your mother the truth.
我们说了谎  妈妈
We lied, ma.
什么叫你们撒了谎
What do you mean you lied?
我们几个  大洋六人
All of us-- the oceanic six,
坠机后发生的事  我们说了谎
We lied about what happened after the crash.
那到底发生什么了
And what did happen?
好吧
Okay.
我们坠机了
See, we did crash,
坠毁到这个疯狂的岛屿
But it was on this crazy island.
我们就等救援  可是没有救援
And we waited for rescue, and there wasn't any rescue.
那有个黑烟怪物
And there was a smoke monster,
后来发现岛上还有其他人
And then there were other people on the island.
我们管他们叫The Others  他们开始攻击我们
We called them the others, and they started attacking us.
后来我们发现了一些舱门
And we found some hatches,
还有个按钮  你每隔108分钟就得按一下  否则
And there was a button you had to push every 108 minutes or...
其实我也不是太清楚
Well, I was never really clear on that.
但是The Others和那些舱没有关系
But... the others didn't have anything to do with the hatches.
那是达摩组织遗留下来的  但是他们都死了
That was the dharma initiative. but they were all dead.
The others杀死了他们  现在又来杀我们
The others killed them, and now they're trying to kill us.
后来我们和The others联手了
And then we teamed up with the others
因为有些坏人开着一艘货船来了
Because some worse people were coming on a freighter.
Desmond女朋友的老爸派的人来杀我们
Desmond's girlfriend's father sent them to kill us.
所以我们偷了他们的直升机
So we stole their helicopter
我们飞向他们的货船  可是船爆炸了
And we flew it to their freighter, but it blew up.
现在我们又回不去岛上
And we couldn't go back to the island
因为岛消失了  我们只能迫降在海上
Because it disappeared, so then we crashed into the ocean,
我们在海上漂了一阵子有艘船过来把我们救了上去
And we floated there for a while Until a boat came and picked us up.
那时  就是我们六个  这部分是真的
And by then, there were six of us. that part was true.
但是
But the...
但是剩下的那些人
But the rest of the people...
他们也曾经和我们一起在飞机上
Who were on the plane?
可他们现在却还在那座岛上
They're still on that island.
我相信你
I believe you.
但是我不明白你的意思
I don't understand you,
但是我相信你
But I believe you.
很多人死了  妈妈
A lot of people died, ma.
这样可怕的事情还在持续发生  因为
And now this bad stuff is happening because...
我们不该撒谎
We shouldn't have lied.
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事  我只是踩到了什么东西
Yeah, I'm fine. I just stepped on something.
什么东西卡住了
Something jammed...
妈的
Son of a bitch.
我们得继续往前走
We should keep moving.
我们得抓紧和其他人在小溪处汇合
We gotta hook up with everybody at the creek.
那是条很长的小溪  James  是在它的哪个部分
It's a long creek, james. which part?
我不知道  可能是比较潮湿的那块
I don't know--the wet part.
如果我不用听他们的
Sorry if my plan's not up to others' stan--
这些人是谁  是你的人吗
Who were those people? Are they yours?
是他们射的箭吗
Did they shoot the arrows?
你想我爬过去然后问问他们吗
You want me to crawl out there and ask 'em?
没说让你耍小聪明  我只是
You don't have to be a wiseass. I'm just trying--
你们在我们岛上做什么呢
What are you doing on our island?!
妈的
Son of a bitch.
给点反映  Sayid
Come on, sayid.
快
Come on.
Sayid
Sayid.
是我  我是Jack
It--it's... it's Jack.
没事了  没事了
It's okay. it's all right.
你没事了
U're okay. you're all right.
发生什么事情了
What happened?
你没事了  你现在在医院里
You're fine. you're in the hospital.
Hurley的爸爸带你来的
Hurley's father brought you to me.
怎么会是Hurley的爸爸
Hurley's father?
Sayid  之前你被攻击了
Sayid, you've been attacked.
Hurley在哪
Where's Hurley?
他和他双亲住在一起
He's at his parents' house.
谁跟他在一起呢
Who's with him?
我不知道  可能是他妈妈
I don't know. his mother, maybe?
还有谁知道他在那吗
Does anyone else know he's there?
你好  Hugo
Hello, Hugo.
离我远点
Get away from me.
快滚
Get away!
Hugo  我知道你现在遇到麻烦事了
Hugo, I know you're in trouble,
我可以向你保证  我会把所有事情解决
And I can assure you I've taken care of everything.
我有辆车  我们可以一起回去
I have a car waiting for us out back.
警察没看见我进来
The police didn't see me come in.
我可以带你离开这里
I can get you out of here.
不必了  老兄
No way, dude.
Sayid已经提醒过我关于你的事了
Sayid warned me about you.
我带你去见Sayid  他现在和Jack在一起
I'm taking you to sayid. he's with Jack.
所以我为什么会在这里  Hugo  是Jack叫我来的
That's why I'm here, Hugo. Jack called me.
要不然我怎么知道他们是在一起的
How else would I know that they're together?
不
No.
你又想玩弄我
You're--you're playing one of your mind games.
他们永远不会相信你的
They would never trust you.
从他们的角度来说  我不是一个容易被信任的人
In their defense, I'm not an easy person to trust.
但是他们却来找我了
But they came around
他们终于明白我们的目的是一致的
When they realized that we all want the same thing.
那是什么
And what's that?
回到岛上
To go back to the island.
跟我们一起走吧  Hugo
Come with us, Hugo...
这一切就会结束  你也不必再躲躲藏藏
And this'll be over. You can stop hiding.
你不用再为我们的故事而担心
You can stop worrying about the stories
更不用担心欺骗别人
And the deceptions.
如果你跟我一起走的话
If you come with me,
就再也不用说谎了
You won't ever have to lie again.
好吗
Please.
让我来帮你吧
Let me help you.
想都别想  老兄
Never, dude.
你们抓到我了
Hey! hey, you got me!
对  你们抓到我了  我就是凶手  停  警察
That's right, you got me! that's right! I'm the killer! stop! police!
把身体转过去  然后朝我走过来  慢慢跪下
Face your back towards me! Slowly drop down to your knees! I'm the killer.
我是个杀人凶手  我杀了四个人  三个人
I'm a murderer. I killed four people... three people.
都是我杀的   快把我带走吧
I killed them all. j-just-- just get me away from here.
快点带我走吧
Just get me out of here.
简洁明了...
I'm gonna make this quite simple for you.
快告诉我  你们在做什么
You're gonna tell me what you're doing,
你们有多少人  你们是怎么来这里的
How many of you there are and how you got here.
如果不是在回答问题  请闭嘴
Unless you're answering my questions, Don't speak.
快说  否则我砍下她的手
I want you to tell me everything or I'll cut off her other hand. what?!
什么
What?!
-Other?  -你没有和我谈条件的资格
- Other?  - the first one isn't negotiable.
我只是在告诉你我不是在开玩笑
It's just to illustrate how serious I am.
不  等等  我们本不应该出现在这儿
No! hold on! hold on! chill out! we're not supposed to be here.
只是这个岛发生了什么事情
Something's happening to the island.
-那个闪光  -砍
- There are these flashes-  - do it!
不  等一下  我会告诉你你想知道的事情
No! wait a second! I'll tell you whatever you want to know!
-快  -不要
- Do it!  - No!
James  Juliet
James. Juliet.
看见你们真高兴
Nice to see ya.
运气好吗
Any luck?
是的
Yes.
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really.
你呢  你怎么样
What about you?
我遇到了一些困难
I'm having some... difficulties.
你最好抓紧时间
Well, you better get busy...
因为你只有七十个小时
Because you only have 70 hours.
不  给我的时间不够  我需要至少
No, no, that's not enough time. I need at least--
你需要什么已经不重要了
What you need is irrelevant.
你只有七十个小时
70 hours is what you've got.
听着  我今晚没能把Reyes带回来
Look, I lost reyes tonight.
如果我不能把他们带回来会怎样
What happens if I can't get them all to come back?
那就等着上帝来帮我们吧
Then god help us all.